southindianactresses.net 2014-04-06

# Privacy Policy | SouthIndianActresses.net

## SouthIndianActresses.net Privacy Policy - An Overview:

SouthIndianActresses.net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for all users of the internet as a whole and our website in particular. 

## Cookies:

While visiting this website, SouthIndianActresses.net's computer servers may gather non-personal information (“cookies”) for the purposes of statistical and market research. A cookie has been described as a piece of data stored on your computer containing information about you. The information obtained from your cookies will be used for the purposes of updating and improving this website. Such information may include, without limitation, the type of browser you are using, the domain name you came from, and other non-personal information. 

## Newsletter:

SouthIndianActresses.net offers a free electronic newsletter to its users. We gather the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. 

## Links:

SouthIndianActresses.net contains links to other websites. Please observe that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website collecting personally identifiable information. 

## Acceptance of our Privacy policy:

Your use of the SouthIndianActresses.net websites signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the SouthIndianActresses.net. This Privacy Policy may be changed from time-to-time without notice. Any such changes will be posted to this web site and will be available for your review. Any continued use of this web site after a change has occurred will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## Contacting the Website:

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us
